<package>
	<id>com.thundermastermind.legacyios</id>
	<name>LegacyiOS</name>
	<version>1.0b1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>7.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>Anemone</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>LegacyiOS is a detailed iOS 6 theme for modern iOS.</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description>LegacyiOS brings back the iOS 6 icons to your iOS 7-11 device with all of iOS 6's pleasing high detail for the Anemone theme engine. All the other themes released in the past just weren't accurate to how iOS 6 looked, so LegacyiOS sets out to do just that with as much detail as possible with the aid of original iOS 6 devices. All icons are properly masked with the bonus of icon shadows and nothing looks out of place whether it be a system app or a 3rd party app that isn’t in the theme.
</description>
		<description><![CDATA[
		SIDE NOTES:<br/> 
		• This package is currently for the the Retina iPhone and iPod Touch only. iPhone Plus and X will work, but won’t look right.<br/>
		• iPhone Plus and X support will arrive soon.<br/>
		• iPad support will arrive soon after the Plus/X package is available.
		]]>
		</description>
		<description><![CDATA[
		What's included:<br/>
		• All stock iOS 6 icons<br/>
		• A few custom icons for system apps that didn't exist in iOS 6<br/>
		• A couple 3rd party app icons (iOS 5 YouTube icon is included)<br/>
		• Icon wallpaper shadows<br/>
		• Dock shadow</br>
		• Option to switch between Helvetica Neue (iOS 6’s system font) and San Francisco for consistency with iOS 9-11’s system font.<br/>
		• Original bold icon labels with shadows<br/>
		• Calendar icon text<br/>
		• iOS 6 badges<br/>
		• Folder icons and background<br/>
		• A few UI sound effects<br/>
		]]>
		</description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description>This is a description for screenshot 1. It's Cydia!</description>
			<image>cydia.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>This is a description for screenshot 2. It's another Cydia!</description>
			<image>cydia.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
		<change>Version 1.0 Beta 1</change>
		<change>Inital release with a lot of things that still need to be added.</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>/r/jailbreak</name>
			<url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
